▍2026 美网女单决赛
莱巴金娜 6-4 5-7 6-2 萨巴伦卡 · 赛后捧杯致辞
Elena, boy, you're good.
埃琳娜 你真了不起
How did you put together a year like that?
这样的一年 你是怎么做到的？
How did you beat
你是怎么击败
the two-time defending champion
那位两连冠的卫冕冠军
the way you did?
而且赢得这么漂亮？
How did you do it?
你是怎么做到的？
Well, it's tough to find words right now.
这会儿真的找不到词
Honestly, I didn't expect nothing like this.
说实话 我完全没想到会是这样
coming to this tournament.
来打这站比赛的时候
I've been dealing a little bit
我一直带着点
with the injury
伤在身上
but somehow everything aligned together
可不知怎么 一切都对上了
on my side and I just want
全站到了我这边 我想说
to say Aryna you are great champion.
阿丽娜 你是了不起的冠军
It's it's so difficult to play against you.
跟你打真的太难了
You pushed to such a limits.
你把我逼到了极限
I was diving on the court and just trying
我在场上一直在扑救 只想
to get all the possible balls
把每一个能碰到的球都救回来
and yeah just congrats to you
也要恭喜你
for all the achievements.
恭喜你拿到的这一切
Congrats to your team.
也恭喜你的团队
You guys doing an amazing job.
你们做得非常出色
really I can't find the words now.
我现在真的找不到词
Sorry.
抱歉
Then I want to say thank you of course
接下来我当然要谢谢
to such a beautiful spectators
这么好的观众们
for amazing atmosphere.
谢谢这么棒的气氛
I honestly I honestly was coming here
说实话 我一直来这儿
for last 10 years
来了整整十年
and it was never successful.
从来没有成功过
Nothing close
甚至都不接近
to that and I mean it's it's just incredible
所以这真的太不可思议了
and I'm falling in love
我越来越爱
in New York more and more and it's
越来越爱纽约 这对我来说
an amazing memories for me.
是一段美好的回忆
Thank you guys.
谢谢你们
Of course,
当然
I want to say thank you to the people
我要谢谢那些人
without who I wouldn't be here.
没有他们 我站不到这儿
It's my team.
那就是我的团队
Thank you so much, guys.
太谢谢你们了
Stefano, Stas, Stefan, Nick,
斯特凡诺 斯塔斯 斯特凡 尼克
my fitness coach, he's back home
我的体能教练 他在家
in front of the TV.
守在电视机前
Of course, my family also back home.
当然 我的家人也在家里
And all my friends, thank you so much,
还有我所有的朋友 谢谢你们
guys.
真的谢谢
You are the best.
你们是最好的
And without you, it won't be possible.
没有你们 这一切都不可能
And last I want
最后我想
to say thank you to all people
谢谢所有的人
who made this tournament possible.
谢谢他们办起了这项赛事
It's an amazing event
这是一项了不起的赛事
and yeah it's I can't find words.
我还是找不到词
This atmosphere
这里的气氛
is just something unbelievable
真的让人难以置信
and doesn't feel real for now.
到现在都觉得不像是真的
So thank you so much to to everyone
所以真的谢谢每一个人
and yeah looking forward
我也很期待
to come back next year.
明年再回到这里
Thank you.
谢谢大家